// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Lemon Is Hybrid Of?",
    answer: "Bitter Orange And Citron",
    options: [
      "Orange And Lime",
      "Bitter Orange And Citron",
      "Sweet Orange And Citron",
      "None Of The Above"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Statue Of Liberty Is Gifted To USA By Which Country?",
    answer: "France",
    options: [
      "France",
      "India",
      "Italy",
      "Russia"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Which Is The Smallest Ocean?",
    answer: "Arctic Ocean",
    options: [
      "Pacific Ocean",
      "Indian Ocean",
      "Atlantic Ocean",
      "Arctic Ocean"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Which Was The Largest Snake In The History Of The World?",
    answer: "Titanoboa Cerrejonensis",
    options: [
      "Anaconda",
      "Python",
      "Titanoboa Cerrejonensis",
      "King Cobra"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Dead Sea Is Located Between Which Two Countries?",
    answer: "Jordan And Israel",
    options: [
      "Jordan And Sudan",
      "Jordan And Israel",
      "Turkey And UAE",
      "UAE And Egypt"
    ]
  },
 
  

   {
    numb: 6,
    question: "In Which Ocean 'Bermunda Triangle' Region Is Located?",
    answer: "Atlantic",
     options: [
       "Indian",
       "Pacific",
       "Atlantic",
       "Arctic"
    ]
   },


   {
    numb: 7,
    question: "Which Country Is Known As The 'Playground Of Europe'?",
    answer: "Switzerland",
     options: [
       "Austia",
       "Switzerland",
       "Holland",
       "Italy"
    ]
   },
   
   {
    numb: 8,
    question: "Which Country Is Known As The 'Land Of ThunderBolts'?",
    answer: "Bhutan",
     options: [
       "Bhutan",
       "China",
       "Venenzula",
       "Thailand"
    ]
   },

   {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Which Continent Has The Highest Number Of Countries?",
    answer: "Africa",
     options: [
       "Asia",
       "Europe",
       "Africa",
       "North America"
    ]
   },

   {
    numb: 10,
    question: "Which Country Has White Elephants?",
    answer: "Thailand",
     options: [
       "Thailand",
       "Sri Lanka",
       "Malasiya",
       "India"
    ]
   },
   
];